Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trial, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Crimson Lions in fifth place?
The new captain of the Crimson Lion Kings is Marilona Vermillion, older sister to Fregolion, who remains gravely wounded and unconscious after battling the Midnight Sun.
This fiery warrior is holding a hot springs training camp in a strong magic region.
Asta and many others have been forced to participate, but once they set their sights on the oasis that awaits them at the summit...
I'm not leaving what I want.
What we want most in the world isn't something you can just achieve through blind luck.
I'll reach the top.
Our dream depends on it! You want results? You got it!
You got it!
I got it!
Get it!
Know what?
I'môtie in a house.
Actually, you got twenty research at yourなら.
You got it!
Thebacks of your 어쩌う in the shop – You got it!
Heightly put upべき of it!
Lots of STARTED
vem
while having any서
extraordinary moments
do you think it's enough?
Do you think it's enough to let you know?
How many times do you think it's enough to take this process?
I can't.
To be continued...
I can't do it the usual way. What I need is a totally different plan. Something unusual.
Right, my new power! But what makes it work? I kind of blacked out the first time and the next thing I knew I looked like that!
What am I doing?!
Thinking so hard that it makes your head explode? Doesn't seem like your style.
Good point. I can't overthink this. I wasn't thinking about anything special the first time, was I?
I just gotta focus and empty my mind.
New power, let's go!
Never mind, you can go home.
Look, let's pretend that didn't happen! I promise you, I can do it if you give me another chance! Really, I'm a can-do kind of person!
Very well. Then at least put up a good fight.
Got it!
Well, yeah, that's my thing. Struggling through to the end is all I know!
Hey, wait. I wasn't just not thinking about anything the first time I used that power. I was dying. That's why I blacked out.
So, maybe I should dive into that magma.
Well, I am the guy who plowed straight into a salamander bomb. This doesn't scare me one bit.
No, that's not it! That would just be reckless and stupid. I can't forget what Fuegolion told me. That it's important to stay calm. I need to think harder.
God, it's no use! Now I can't think of anything! Man, I really am an idiot!
That monoskin barrier thing is pretty awesome. Gee, it's too bad I don't have any magic power.
This is weird. I haven't been upset about that in a long time.
Hey, wait a minute, Asta! Quit being jealous of other people! There's plenty of stuff you can...
I don't see how a fool who doesn't even know himself can achieve anything great!
Don't know myself? Maybe that's it!
What if I just don't have a very good understanding of the powers I have?
Okay, number one. I've got this anti-magic sword that only I can use because I don't have magic power of my own.
It slices through any spell, but in a place like this, it's pretty much useless.
Number two. The strength and stamina to wield that sword.
They're good for regular mountain climbing, but this volcano is more than I can physically tackle.
Number three. Thanks to Captain Yami, I've got the ability to sense ki, which I'm using right now.
It helps me pick up on erupting lava and falling rocks.
Great!
A person's glance, their breathing, their scent, the way their muscles move, the hint of their presence.
Taken together, all of that living energy people give off, that's called ki.
That's my fighting style. I combine the ability to sense ki with my magic and the strength of my muscles.
Maybe if I use ki on myself, I can get a read on that crazy new power.
I knew it. I can feel my own ki inside me.
Plus there's some kind of black energy coming from my anti-magic sword.
If I can make it stronger somehow, and figure out a way to get it moving through my entire body, like a river?
No, a circle. Now I just need to picture it.
There we go. Perfect.
This stance is helping the power circulate all over me.
But I'm not done. Not yet.
It needs more intensity.
The amplified anti-magic transferring from the sword into Asta's body caused him to undergo a sudden physical change.
That's it! My strength is overflowing! This should take me straight to the summit!
I can't stop!
What? No way! Why isn't that attack working?
Hold your ground!
If we can't defeat this thing, then we've got no right to call ourselves Magic Knight!
Yeah! Now teach it a lesson, Leopold!
Got it!
Wait a minute! You're the one who should have the advantage with your water magic, but you haven't lifted a finger to help us!
What's up with that?
Not that it's any of your business, but it's already taking everything I've got to keep my mana skin on.
Asta?
Why does he look like that?
Aaaaaah!
One horn full for us, go!
Ha ha ha! That's what I call a rival! I see you learned yourself a new technique! And with that whole edgy look you've got now, I say we call you Black Osta!
Aaaaaah!
Hey! Where are you going?
Big speed!
I don't know how to stuff fly it, but it looks like I'm headed for the pink, so I'll just go with the flow for now!
Is that...
You don't!
Hehehehe!
I don't want to land in magma!
Aren't you going to help him?
There wouldn't be much point. The anti-magic power bubbling up inside of him isn't interested in the magma. Not at all. It's after strong magic.
Aaaaaah!
She's pulling me in! Hey! You should probably run!
Run?
Aaaaaah!
Little fool!
Don't you know female lions are the hunters?
Aaaaaah!
She's pulling me in! Hey! You should probably run!
Run? Little fool! Don't you know female lions are the hunters?
Flame magic!
Huh?
I should have guessed it.
That crazy old crimson lioness wouldn't be herself if she didn't have her claws out. There's
no way he could have dodged that in mid-air. Hey! You still alive down there, kid?
Whoa! That was amazing! Yup, she's definitely Feigolion's sister!
You seem like you're getting to know yourself a little better now, but you're not finished
yet.
Right!
I couldn't control my power, but at least I used it. Okay, I'm gonna train real hard
and pass the Royal Knights exam! If being a part of that squad means you're one of the
best, then that's what I want to do!
It took you long enough to make it this far, you fools! Yuleturn Volcano was inactive and
completely harmless during the night, so at this point, it isn't much of an accomplishment
on your part!
It's just embarrassing! At this rate, our squad will never return to first! If you didn't
make it up here before nightfall, you'll do it again tomorrow!
Yes, ma'am!
I got here in time, so that doesn't apply to me, but I'd be happy to do it again a hundred
times if it means I can become stronger than Feigolion!
Pathetic! What about ten thousand?
Totally!
Alright! You slugs are now free to enjoy the hot spring!
Finally!
Back in Hodge Village, I used to love a good post-training soak!
Hold on, though. Why don't I see a hot spring anywhere?
Whoa! Amazing! Look at how tall!
Check it out! You know that bath is enormous! This is the best hot spring I've ever seen!
It's something...
These are extremely restorative waters! Best in the kingdom! But not just anybody can waltz in here!
It's very exclusive! A rare and special treat!
That's only because people turn back or get killed on their way up here!
Alright, imbeciles! Get naked!
Hang on a second, sis! We can't do that right here out in the open like this!
I can't get naked! There are girls here, you know! Are we all gonna faint together or what?
That old hot head must have burned out her last brain cell if she thinks that'll happen!
There's no way I'm letting my Yuno take off his clothes in front of all these other women!
In a hot spring? With Yami?
I like a woman who appreciates these things.
It's a nice feeling to have someone wash your back for you every now and then, don't you think?
Goodness! Why does my mind have to wander onto such improper subjects?!
Just stay calm, Charlotte! You mustn't let anyone see that you're flustered!
I can't do this!
I'm not gonna let a bunch of men see shards rockin' body!
Now Earth's magic! Earthen wall partition!
If any one of you scum tries to climb this, your life's as good as over!
That's really smart!
Now guys and girls don't have to bathe together!
See?
All fixed!
It's time to get in there!
Yeah!
Didn't I tell you this hot spring was incredible?!
The view's pretty spectacular, isn't it?
And the water temperature is just right!
Oh wow! Char is so gorgeous! Did I die and go to Heaven?
Cause this is great!
There's nothing better than a refreshing drink while you soak in a hot spring!
Charlotte! You wanna knock one back?
No thank you, I'll pass.
No! What's wrong with my drinks?! Not fancy enough?!
What? No, that isn't the problem at all!
I have utmost respect for you, Lady Mary Leona!
Well, drink with me then!
Disgracing myself in front of Yami at the Star Festival was bad enough!
But now? While I'm naked? Far too risky!
I'll have one with you!
I may not look like it, but I'm actually a lot older than either of you!
Ah! The wind spirit, eh?
That wall's not going to suddenly disappear, is it?
Wow, you're spaced out!
Hey! Stop that! I can wash my hair myself!
It's okay, let me do it!
You're Noelle, right?
I think gutsy girls like you are the best kind in the world!
You wanna join the Blue Rose Knights?!
Hm? But I'm already a member of the Black Bulls!
Come on! It's just a grubby old boys club! What's so special about it?!
Oh, I wouldn't say that!
It is mostly guys, but we do have a couple of strong women!
Sure, a few of our members are loudmouthed idiots!
But it's not like it's the worst!
Well, in the Blue Rose Knights, the real members are all women!
We just use the men as errant boys!
I was looking forward to bringing that Yuno kid on board and working into the bone!
But who knew he would end up being that powerful?
The men are just lackeys!
That doesn't sound too bad!
Past that wall is the men's bath!
So, right now, the army is...
Naked?
Completely naked?
You haven't had a single drink!
Why are you unconscious?
One sip is all it takes for you?
My...
Wow, Char, you're even beautiful when you pass out!
I do hope you're okay, though!
So, please call me Captain.
Righty-ho, Char!
And me too!
What happened over there?
The water's perfect.
Beautiful stars.
Lady Asier was especially fond of the view of the night sky from here.
My mother came here? I didn't know.
She did indeed. In fact, she's the one who told me about this place to begin with.
What kind of person was she? I want to know everything.
I mean, no one ever tells me anything about her, so I'm kind of in the dark.
She was very strong.
She gave me lessons all the time.
I may be undefeated in battle, but I was never victorious against her, regardless of the fact that my magic affinity should have given me an advantage.
The steel princess whirled around the battlefield, Asier Silva. Her strength and beauty captivated one and all.
In terms of your looks, you resemble her a lot. Spitting image, even. But your magic powers another story. Your control is sloppy, to say the least. Makes it hard to believe you're her daughter. Her magic was refined to an unparalleled degree. It was so dignified. But despite your royal status, your magic is ugly and coarse. Work hard. Improve.
Improve. You don't have her strength, but you're enough like her that you can overcome that.
Okay. That's right. Asta's improving and he doesn't have any magic. Lacking ability doesn't mean you should run away or make excuses. And now I'm fired up. My body's all warm too.
Did it get hotter in here?
You think you're hot stuff, huh? Bet you can't handle this heat. I'll wipe that little smirk right off your face!
Oh, this is nothing for me.
Now I'm really angry!
Don't let him fool you, Leo! There's nothing cool about him! He just hates losing too much to quit! Gah! Now that I think about it, I'm the same way!
Okay! Whoever stays in here the longest is the winner! Go!
Hey! No fear! Using wind to cool the water down like that is totally cheating!
Cheating? I'm just using my magic. You know, kinda like you're doing to heat up the water.
The hell are you useless morons doing now? There are better ways to enjoy a hot spring!
There are? Like what, Captain?
Oh, I know strength training! It's gotta be strength training! Cause nothing's better than strength training unless it's more strength training!
Shut it, cupcake! I swear you've got muscles where your brain should be. Nobody but you actually likes doing that crap.
Please don't squish me, Captain Yami, sir!
Wait, it's not strength training? Another guy with muscles instead of brains.
Okay, I give. Will you please let go of me and tell us a better way to enjoy the hot springs than strength training?
Isn't it obvious? Getting a look into the women's bath.
Wait, does he mean like, spying? I'm not sure that's such a good idea.
If they caught us doing it, we'd be worse than dead.
Listen to the bunch of you whining like a pack of beardless boys. A man's got to explore the unknown, even if it costs his life.
Exploring the unknown? Is that what it means to be a man?
Jeez, you idiots have a lot to learn. You wanna take a look too, don't you, Mr. Cool?
Meh, not interested.
I'm sick of you, boy, and your high and mighty act. Think you're a lady killer, huh?
No, I don't. No, please stop. I'm just not that kind of guy, that's all.
And exactly what kind of guy are you implying I am, Mr. Cool? Because I don't think I like it.
Please let him go, Captain Yami! He plays it cool, but you lose a sheltered village can. As far as I know, he's got zero experience with women!
Now that I think about it, my brother likes baths too.
Leopold, there's still so much that I need to teach you, but I'm not sure you're ready yet.
Please! I'm ready!
Wait, is it possible? Could this be what my brother wanted to teach me back then?
Leopold, are you prepared to learn the art of spying on naked women?
Heck yeah! I'm ready!
That would never happen! No way!
No. My brother wouldn't peep, not in a million years. In fact, I bet he'd beat up anyone who did.
What are you mumbling about over there, matchstick? Comparing yourself to Captain Sirius is a cop-out. You need to focus on moving past that guy.
That's right. If I push myself, I can be more than my brother.
What are you all standing around for? In some ways, this is a battle. Are you afraid of getting killed or something? Didn't your captain bring you all out here to prove you're not a bunch of cowards?
He's right!
You don't run away from a battle! You stand and fight!
The mighty Crimson Lion Kings don't back down!
Yeah! Time to peep! Let's show him who we are!
Alright, let's do this!
Um, what was that? It sounds like those disgusting men!
Ah, they're so determined in the face of certain death. Maybe there's some hope left for them after all.
They're coming here to peep at us!
Well, they won't get a look at Char's immaculate body, that's for sure!
Now, Earth magic!
Gear Cliff Wall!
Man, so close!
Go!
We're the Crimson Lion Kings! A little wall won't keep us out!
Yeah!
Unbelievable.
Right? Go on, kid. You climbed a volcano today. Scaling that wall should be a piece of cake.
No! I've already got my heart set on somebody special and I refuse to betray her like that!
Okay...
Okay?
And thus ends the Obligatory Hot Springs Episode.
Man, it's the Kingdom...
passion for które
Șicale
Vem
喜歡
ities
I'll make it true, my song, my days
この世界に響かせいこう
駆け抜けたい日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
曲がりくなった道さどくらぐら
輝ける明日を映すメロディ
クローバークリップ
Lily always lifts the villagers' spirits with her gentle smile
When she needs to unwind, this hot spring in Hajj helps to revitalize her
But sometimes, the hot spring isn't enough to dispel her fatigue after a long day of work at the church
That's when she turns to vinegared pot potatoes
They're recommended by the priest himself
Just a few bites and your cares start to slip away
Buy now and receive a free bottle of Bogoro leaf juice with garlic extract
Order soon, supplies won't last long
Starring in a home shopping show?
I knew you had it in you, Sister Lily
Hello everyone, it's sure been a while
Asa and Yuno are both trying so hard
Everyone back at the church is thrilled
Black Clover, page 73
The Royal Knight Selection Test
I hope those boys don't get themselves hurt
David and at rabbin on the bench
The Royal Knight Selection Test
ina
Five Centre Test
There is a rate that is fin af
Power blab
Go in and pose